<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Box2D on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/box2d/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Box2D on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/box2d/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features:  4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:33:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:27:51 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features:  Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:25:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features:  Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:21:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features:  Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
