<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arcade on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/arcade/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arcade on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/arcade/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features:  4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:40:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features:  Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drift Boss</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/drift-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:37:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/drift-boss/</guid>
      <description>Drift your car like a boss. Drift left and right with good timing.
Concentrate and anticipate your drifts and skids in tight spots.
How many points can you score?
Features:  Great arcade 3d environment Unlock cool vehicles by collecting more points. Unlock trucks, taxis, police cars, ice cream trucks, ambulances, firetrucks and more. Full responsive design Full screen capability Great soundtracknd theme.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:30:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:36:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features  Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bobblehead Soccer Royale</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:21:40 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bobblehead-soccer-royale/</guid>
      <description>Move your bobblehead soccer stars around the field. Kick the goals into the opponent&amp;rsquo;s goal.
Collect the powerups to gain an edge over your opponents.
Features:  Mad physics that trumps realism Fun and vibrant soccer atmosphere Funny caricature expressions Challenge over 20+ top soccer players in the world Increasingly challenging levels. Get to Level 3 and the game really heats up. Forget FIFA World Cup, fans of puppet soccer fans will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:55:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features:  Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Baseball</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/ultimate-baseball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:08:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/ultimate-baseball/</guid>
      <description>Swing high, middle or low to hit the ball. Find your sweet spot and perfect timing. Hit correctly and score a baseball home run!
A simple arcade style baseball game for the fans.
Features:  Simple controls to hit high, medium or low Baseball stadium theme, great for brand exposure The game gets more challenging as you score more home runs! Possibility of integrating a high score leaderboard to compete with other players.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
