<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventure on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/adventure/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adventure on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/adventure/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features:  4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:33:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:30:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
