<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brain on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/brain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brain on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:47:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/brain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:47:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features:  Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stupid Zombies</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:46:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/stupid-zombies/</guid>
      <description>One man, one shotgun and a whole lot of zombies. You are humanity&amp;rsquo;s last hope, and it&amp;rsquo;s your job to keep them brainless.
Adjust your shots and angles, and you watch your bullets ricochet from wall to wall, elegantly picking off each zombie&amp;rsquo;s arms and limbs.
Features:  4 giant stages with over 360 challenging levels Exciting zombie theme Simple and innovative ricochet based gameplay. Defeat the stupid zombies with brains and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kill the Spy</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/kill-the-spy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:43:03 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/kill-the-spy/</guid>
      <description>Armed with your trusty pistol, it&amp;rsquo;s up to you, Agent 007 to eliminate the enemy spy agents.
Tap on the correct blocks to eliminate the spy agents. Use the least amount of moves to earn more stars.
Do not hard the hostages, or else the mission will fail.
Features:  Innovative physics and game mechanics. Aim your spy pistol to split structures into multiple pieces Collect treasures to increase your score Place your shots correctly to earn more stars Spy theme and sound effects  Fans of James Bond , Men in Black and spy themed novels will love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:30:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bomb the Bridge</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bomb-the-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:27:51 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/bomb-the-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Plant C4 bombs anywhere on the bridge.
Wait for enemy troops to cross, then detonate them.
Blow up 100% of the bridge and eliminate all troops to score 3 stars.
Features:  Realistic physics Addictive theme Challenging levels Blow up armies, military trucks and tanks!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Onect Connect</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/onect-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:23:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/onect-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect fruit tiles of the same image.
A game of creativity, problem solving and cognitive enhancement.
Use fewer than 3 lines. Only 2 tiles per connection. This is not a match 3 game, but rather a match 2 game that focuses on spatial training and puzzle solving.
Features  3 difficulty levels. Easy, medium and hard Randomized set, every time you play. Ensure unlimited gameplay. Casual theme, suitable for all ages and families Ability to shuffle the set Huge set for long periods of gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:39:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features:  Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:25:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features:  Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connect the Roads</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/connect-the-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:19:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/connect-the-roads/</guid>
      <description>Your car needs to get to work! Move the road tiles to complete the road.
Can you get three stars for each level?
Features:  Simple draggable tiles Fun city theme Turn grid on or off 24 challenging levels guaranteed to twist your brain Fans of pipe games and picture sliders will love this game.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
