<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animals on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/animals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animals on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:47:45 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Seashore Treasure</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/seashore-treasure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:47:45 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/seashore-treasure/</guid>
      <description>Tap an item to pick it up.
Next, pick up a new item that you haven&amp;rsquo;t picked up before.
Continue doing so, until you reach the limit.
Pick up cool items such as sun shades, sea shells, turtles, jellyfish, shorts, sun screen, fish, seahorses and more.
Features:  Fun, relaxed beach and sunny theme Measure your cognitive ability and improve your memory 3 different beaches Beautiful sea shore graphics and animation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:40:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features:  Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:33:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:30:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Coloring Book</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:41:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-coloring-book/</guid>
      <description>Showcase your kids creativity via this coloring book, featuring Didi and Friends.
A fun, all-digital and reusable coloring book built for kids, parents and pre-school institutions.
Features:  Multiple Didi &amp;amp; Friends themed templates to start with Choose different brush sizes and colours Full screen mode for immersive experience Did something wrong? Undo your colors via an eraser Save your works and print them. This feature is great for classrooms Color interesting characters from the Didi &amp;amp; Friends universe, including Didi, Nana, Jojo, Tatak, Bingo and Pak Atan, Positive theme, to foster good vibes via colouring  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Didi and Friends Guess What</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:39:13 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/didi-and-friends-guess-what/</guid>
      <description>Didi and Friends, popular kids animation with over 1 billion views on Youtube is here with a brand new game.
Guess the hidden character, then drag and drop the matching picture to reveal it.
Teach your kids and toddlers to spot patterns, and get rewarded with happy smiles from Didi the Chicken and his friends!
Features:  Fun and vibrant theme, guaranteed to excite kids, preschoolers and toddlers. Simple gameplay suitable for kids Fullscreen mode Learn everyday objects, animals, environmental elements and above all, the brand new set of Didi and Friends characters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:36:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features  Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Bears</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 22:25:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/love-bears/</guid>
      <description>Draw lines and shapes to bump the bears. Find a way to bring the two love bears together.
Everything you draw turns into real objects!
Collect 3 stars for every level successfully completed.
Features:  Beautiful scenery and theme. Addictive tracing gameplay. Draw anything. Over 30 challenging levels per episode. Extremely cute pastel color theme. Cute bears with hats, glasses, panda caps and more! Suitable for all ages. Fans of Love Balls and Happy Glass will enjoy this game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
