<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Endless Runner on MarketJS Game Gallery</title>
    <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/endless-runner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Endless Runner on MarketJS Game Gallery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:40:30 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/tags/endless-runner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dinosaur Run</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:40:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dinosaur-run/</guid>
      <description>Play a cute and lovable T-Rex running across a desert.
Time your dino jumps to avoid the different obstacles.
How high can you score?
Features:  Cool pixel artwork with T Rex dinosaur. Classic grayscale theme set in prehistoric era. Jump over a variety of plants and cactus. Easy to play, hard to master. The background accelerates and decelerates occasionally, to keep you on your toes. Responsive design with fullscreen capability Works great on Chrome and any modern HTML5 browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil Hunt</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:33:19 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/oil-hunt/</guid>
      <description>Stretch out a pipe in order to strike oil.
Hit it big as you guide oil-hungry heroes and monsters in a mystical wasteland! Aim for the highest score, and unlock funny characters!
Explore different lands - from long stretching savannas, to green hills, sandy beaches and dark marshes - you’ll be surprised at all the places you’ll find where you can just stick a pipe and watch as tons of fantastic tasty dark stuff spill out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dumb Ways to Die 2 the Games</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 09:30:17 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/dumb-ways-to-die-2-the-games/</guid>
      <description>Dumb Ways to Die is back with a bigger and better sequel to the original.
In Dumb Ways To Die 2 - The Games, now you can access various maps and locations to try out even more fun and dangerous challenges.
Collect tokens to unlock different aspects of the city, while complete mini challenges perfectly (or imperfectly, depending on how you play). Score points to keep your ranking high.
Play in cool locations such as Adrenaland, Drown Town, Dumbest of the Dumb, and Freezerville.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cam and Leon Donut Hop</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 23:36:52 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/cam-and-leon-donut-hop/</guid>
      <description>Brought to you by the creators of a 3D animation, Cam and Leon Donut Hop features 2 funny and cute characters, hopping their way around the park.
Hop in and out of donuts, but don&amp;rsquo;t hit the obstacles!
Features  Interactive tutorial Easy to play, hard to master Increasingly challenging obstacles Unlock different characters as you progress. Gain access to Leon, Ladybird, Ice Cube and Pepper Shaker!  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpha Space Invasion</title>
      <link>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/alpha-space-invasion/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:55:11 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>ttps://andrian-alfarabi-impact360.github.io/public-hugo-gallery/games/alpha-space-invasion/</guid>
      <description>Alpha sector is under invasion. Young pilot, your task is simple. Warp into the sector, and destroy enemy spacecraft before they destroy you.
Avoid the asteroids and keep your shields high. Rake up as many hits as you can!
Features:  Interactive tutorial Simple controls (keyboard on desktop, touch controls on mobile) Endless gameplay Fans of sci-fi movies such as Star Wars, Star Trek, Battlestar Galactica and Guardians of the Galaxy will - love this game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
